[   {"question": "book", "answer": "本", "sound":"hon"},
    {"question": "electricity", "answer": "電", "sound":"den"},
    {"question": "what", "answer": "何", "sound":"nani"},
    {"question": "yen", "answer": "円", "sound":"en"},
    {"question": "name", "answer": "名", "sound":"na"},
    {"question": "half", "answer": "半", "sound":"han"},
    {"question": "car", "answer": "車", "sound":"kuruma"},
    {"question": "way", "answer": "道", "sound":"miti"},
    {"question": "country", "answer": "国", "sound":"kuni"},
    {"question": "school", "answer": "校", "sound":"kou"},
    {"question": "study", "answer": "学", "sound":"gakku"},
    {"question": "company", "answer": "社", "sound":"sha"},
    {"question": "meet", "answer": "会", "sound":"kai"},
    {"question": "shop", "answer": "店", "sound":"mise"},
    {"question": "station", "answer": "駅", "sound":"eki"},
    {"question": "fish", "answer": "魚", "sound":"sakana"},
    {"question": "horse", "answer": "馬", "sound":"uma"},
    {"question": "cow", "answer": "牛", "sound":"usi"},
    {"question": "rest", "answer": "休", "sound":"kyu"},
    {"question": "listen", "answer": "聞", "sound":"bun"},
    {"question": "buy", "answer": "買", "sound":"bai"},
    {"question": "language", "answer": "語", "sound":"go"},
    {"question": "speak", "answer": "話", "sound":"hanasi"},
    {"question": "read", "answer": "読", "sound":"doku"},
    {"question": "enter", "answer": "入", "sound":"nyu"},
    {"question": "exit", "answer": "出", "sound":"shutsu"},
    {"question": "stand", "answer": "立", "sound":"ritsu"},
    {"question": "say", "answer": "言", "sound":"gen"},
    {"question": "look", "answer": "見", "sound":"ken"},
    {"question": "write", "answer": "書", "sound":"sho"},
    {"question": "drink", "answer": "飲", "sound":"in"},
    {"question": "eat", "answer": "食", "sound":"shoku"},
    {"question": "come", "answer": "来", "sound":"rai"},
    {"question": "go", "answer": "行", "sound":"gyo"},
    {"question": "white", "answer": "白", "sound":"siro"},
    {"question": "early", "answer": "早", "sound":"sou"},
    {"question": "long", "answer": "長", "sound":"chou"},
    {"question": "few", "answer": "少", "sound":"shou"},
    {"question": "many", "answer": "多", "sound":"ta"},
    {"question": "comfort", "answer": "安", "sound":"an"},
    {"question": "high", "answer": "高", "sound":"kou"},
    {"question": "old", "answer": "古", "sound":"ko"},
    {"question": "new", "answer": "新", "sound":"shin"},
    {"question": "small", "answer": "小", "sound":"sho"},
    {"question": "big", "answer": "大", "sound":"dai"},
    {"question": "air", "answer": "気", "sound":"ki"},
    {"question": "heaven", "answer": "天", "sound":"ten"},
    {"question": "sky", "answer": "空", "sound":"sora"},
    {"question": "rain", "answer": "雨", "sound":"ame"},
    {"question": "flower", "answer": "花", "sound":"hana"},
    {"question": "river", "answer": "川", "sound":"kawa"},
    {"question": "mountain", "answer": "山", "sound":"yama"},
    {"question": "behind", "answer": "後", "sound":"ato"},
    {"question": "front", "answer": "前", "sound":"mae"},
    {"question": "outside", "answer": "外", "sound":"soto"},
    {"question": "inside", "answer": "中", "sound":"naka"},
    {"question": "north", "answer": "北", "sound":"kita"},
    {"question": "south", "answer": "南", "sound":"minami"},
    {"question": "west", "answer": "西", "sound":"nisi"},
    {"question": "east", "answer": "東", "sound":"higasi"},
    {"question": "right", "answer": "右", "sound":"migi"},
    {"question": "left", "answer": "左", "sound":"hidari"},
    {"question": "down", "answer": "下", "sound":"sita"},
    {"question": "up", "answer": "上", "sound":"ue"},
    {"question": "power", "answer": "力", "sound":"tikara"},
    {"question": "leg", "answer": "足", "sound":"asi"},
    {"question": "hand", "answer": "手", "sound":"te"},
    {"question": "ear", "answer": "耳", "sound":"mimi"},
    {"question": "mouth", "answer": "口", "sound":"kuti"},
    {"question": "eye", "answer": "目", "sound":"me"},
    {"question": "friend", "answer": "友", "sound":"tomo"},
    {"question": "life", "answer": "生", "sound":"shou"},
    {"question": "ahead", "answer": "先", "sound":"saki"},
    {"question": "child", "answer": "子", "sound":"ko"},
    {"question": "mother", "answer": "母", "sound":"haha"},
    {"question": "father", "answer": "父", "sound":"titi"},
    {"question": "woman", "answer": "女", "sound":"onna"},
    {"question": "man", "answer": "男", "sound":"otoko"},
    {"question": "human", "answer": "人", "sound":"hito"},
    {"question": "while/ between", "answer": "間", "sound":"kan"},
    {"question": "time", "answer": "時", "sound":"ji"},
    {"question": "minute", "answer": "分", "sound":"fun"},
    {"question": "noon", "answer": "午", "sound":"go"},
    {"question": "every", "answer": "毎", "sound":"mai"},
    {"question": "now", "answer": "今", "sound":"ima"},
    {"question": "year", "answer": "年", "sound":"nen"},
    {"question": "week", "answer": "週", "sound":"shuu"},
    {"question": "sun", "answer": "日", "sound":"niti"},
    {"question": "soil", "answer": "土", "sound":"dou"},
    {"question": "gold", "answer": "金", "sound":"kin"},
    {"question": "tree", "answer": "木", "sound":"moku"},
    {"question": "water", "answer": "水", "sound":"sui"},
    {"question": "fire", "answer": "火", "sound":"ka"},
    {"question": "moon", "answer": "月", "sound":"getsu"},
     {"question": "ten thousand", "answer": "万", "sound":"man"},
     {"question": "thousand", "answer": "千", "sound":"jyu"},
     {"question": "hundred", "answer": "百", "sound":"jyu"},
     {"question": "ten", "answer": "十", "sound":"jyu"},
    {"question": "nine", "answer": "九", "sound":"kyu"},
    {"question": "eight", "answer": "八", "sound":"hati"},
    {"question": "seven", "answer": "七", "sound":"siti"},
    {"question": "six", "answer": "六", "sound":"roku"},
    {"question": "five", "answer": "五", "sound":"go"},
    {"question": "four", "answer": "四", "sound":"yon"},
    {"question": "three", "answer": "三", "sound":"san"},
    {"question": "two", "answer": "二", "sound":"ni"},
    {"question": "one", "answer": "一", "sound":"iti"}
]